// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
        {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the term for the amount of money that a borrower owes to a lender?",
        answer: "Debt",
        options: [
          "Credit",
          "Equality",
          "Debt",
          "Investment"
        ]
      },
        {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is the difference between a debit card and a credit card?",
        answer: "A debit card allows you to spend money you already have in your bank account, while a credit card allows you to borrow money that you'll have to pay back later with interest.",
        options: [
          "A debit card allows you to spend money you already have in your bank account, while a credit card allows you to borrow money that you'll have to pay back later with interest.",
          "A debit card allows you to spend money you already have in your bank account, while a credit card allows you to borrow money that you'll have to pay back later with interest.",
          "A debit card and a credit card are the same thing.",
          "A debit card is a type of loan, while a credit card allows you to spend money you already have in your bank account."
        ]
      },
        {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is the term for the percentage of interest that a lender charges on a loan?",
        answer: "Interest rate",
        options: [
          " Dividend",
          "Yield",
          "Interest rate",
          "Coupon rate"
        ]
      },
        {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the term for a financial institution that accepts deposits from customers and provides loans?",
        answer: "Bank",
        options: [
          "Insurance company",
          "Credit union",
          "Bank",
          "Investment firm"
        ]
      },
        {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the name of the government agency responsible for regulating banks and other financial institutions in Nepal?",
        answer: "Nepal Rastra Bank (NRB)",
        options: [
          "Private Placement",
          "Initial Public Offering (IPO)",
          "Nepal Rastra Bank (NRB)",
          "Department of the Treasury"
        ]
      },
      {
           numb: 6,
           question: "What is the term for the amount of money that an investor puts into a company in exchange for ownership?",
           answer: "Equity",
           options: [
             "Interest",
             "Dividend",
             "Capital gains",
             "Equity"
           ]
         },
         {
                numb: 7,
                question: "What is the term for a diversified portfolio of investments designed to maximize returns and minimize risk?",
                answer: "Mutual Fund",
                options: [
                  "Mutual Fund",
                  "Hedge Fund",
                  "Pension",
                  "Index Fund"
                ]
              },
              {
                numb: 8,
                question: "What is the name of the process by which a company goes public and offers shares of stock for sale to the public?",
                answer: "Initial Public Offering(IPO)",
                options: [
                  "Secondary Offering",
                  "Private Placement",
                  "Initial Public Offering(IPO)",
                  "Buyback"
                ]
              },
              {
                numb: 9,
                question: "What is the name of the financial statement that shows a company's revenues, expenses, and profits over a period of time?",
                answer: "Income Statement",
                options: [
                  "Balance Sheet",
                  "Cash Flow Statement",
                  "Statement of retained earnings",
                  "Income Statement"
                ]
              },
              {
                numb: 10,
                question: "What is the term for the total value of all goods and services produced in a country in a given year?",
                answer: "Gross domestic product (GDP)",
                options: [
                  "Gross domestic product (GDP)",
                  "Consumer price index (CPI)",
                  "Inflation rate",
                  "National income"
                ]
              },


      // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
      // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
    
      //   {
      //   numb: 6,
      //   question: "Your Question is Here",
      //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
      //   options: [
      //     "Option 1",
      //     "option 2",
      //     "option 3",
      //     "option 4"
      //   ]
      // },
    ];